{
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "How many ducks are in a goose?",
            "prompts": [
                "1",
                "2",
                "3"
            ],
            "answer": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the first US president to live in the white house?",
            "prompts": [
                "George Washington",
                "Alexander Hamilton",
                "John Adams"
            ],
            "answer": "John Adams"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the first dog in space?",
            "prompts": [
                "Balto",
                "Laika",
                "Toto"
            ],
            "answer": "Laika"
        },
        {
            "question": "What festival falls on the first day of the Chinese New Year?",
            "prompts": [
                "Winter Festival",
                "Lunar Festival",
                "Spring Festival"
            ],
            "answer": "Spring Festival"
        },
        {
            "question": "What animal was the Egyptian God Horus depicted as?",
            "prompts": [
                "Falcon",
                "Cat",
                "Dog"
            ],
            "answer": "Falcon"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the capital of East Germany?",
            "prompts": [
                "Hamburg",
                "Munich",
                "East Berlin"
            ],
            "answer": "East Berlin"
        },
        {
            "question": "In 'The Wizard of Oz', what was the lion in search of?",
            "prompts": [
                "Heart",
                "Brain",
                "Courage"
            ],
            "answer": "Courage"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Thor's hammer?",
            "prompts": [
                "Jarnbjorn",
                "Mjolnir",
                "Gungnir"
            ],
            "answer": "Mjolnir"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Mario character has appeared in all but one 'Mario Party' game?",
            "prompts": [
                "Bowser",
                "Daisy",
                "Wario"
            ],
            "answer": "Wario"
        },
        {
            "question": "In The Simpsons, which character died by getting hit with T-shirts?",
            "prompts": [
                "Maude",
                "Frank Grimes",
                "Fat Tony"
            ],
            "answer": "Maude"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the game 'Joust', what animal was your mount?",
            "prompts": [
                "A Unicorn",
                "A Pegasus",
                "An Ostritch"
            ],
            "answer": "An Ostritch"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the Japanese art of flower arrangement called?",
            "prompts": [
                "Rokkugaden",
                "Ikebana",
                "Heiwa"
            ],
            "answer": "Ikebana"
        },
        {
            "question": "What would a sommelier recommend to you?",
            "prompts": [
                "Shoes",
                "Flowers",
                "Wine"
            ],
            "answer": "Wine"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the main substance found in bones?",
            "prompts": [
                "Cartilage",
                "Calcium",
                "Collagen"
            ],
            "answer": "Collagen"
        },
        {
            "question": "`Mach One` refers to the speed of what?",
            "prompts": [
                "Sound",
                "Frequency",
                "Light"
            ],
            "answer": "Sound"
        },
        {
            "question": "What type of cloud is often described as 'cotton-like'?",
            "prompts": [
                "Stratus",
                "Cumulus",
                "Cirrus"
            ],
            "answer": "Cumulus"
        },
        {
            "question": "What are the lakes of Titan made of?",
            "prompts": [
                "Methane",
                "Water",
                "Hydrogen"
            ],
            "answer": "Methane"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the middle color in a rainbow?",
            "prompts": [
                "Orange",
                "Yellow",
                "Green"
            ],
            "answer": "Green"
        },
        {
            "question": "What causes the holes in Swiss cheese?",
            "prompts": [
                "Mice",
                "Bacteria",
                "Sticks"
            ],
            "answer": "Bacteria"
        },
        {
            "question": "What animal has the most teeth?",
            "prompts": [
                "Sharks",
                "Kraken",
                "Snail"
            ],
            "answer": "Snail"
        },
        {
            "question": "Greenland is part of which kingdom?",
            "prompts": [
                "England",
                "Finland",
                "Denmark"
            ],
            "answer": "Denmark"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Harry Potter's pet owl?",
            "prompts": [
                "Errol",
                "Hedwig",
                "Pigwidgeon"
            ],
            "answer": "Hedwig"
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the last album recorded by The Beatles?",
            "prompts": [
                "Revolver",
                "Abbey Road",
                "Help!"
            ],
            "answer": "Abbey Road"
        },
        {
            "question": "Any color plus white is called what?",
            "prompts": [
                "Tint",
                "Tone",
                "Shade"
            ],
            "answer": "Tint"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Johnny Depp's character in 'Pirates of the Caribbean' movie franchise?",
            "prompts": [
                "Jack Falcon",
                "Jack Sparrow",
                "Jack Dragonfly"
            ],
            "answer": "Jack Sparrow"
        },
        {
            "question": "How many brothers did Ryan lose in the movie 'Saving Private Ryan'?",
            "prompts": [
                "2",
                "3",
                "4"
            ],
            "answer": "3"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Zorro's horse?",
            "prompts": [
                "Tornado",
                "Hurricane",
                "Stormfront"
            ],
            "answer": "Tornado"
        }
    ]
}